http://www.ctscement.com/about/privacy/

PROFESSIONALS
Construction& Design Professionals
For architects, contractors, engineers, DOT personnel, and other professionals who work on residential, commercial, industrial, or infrastructure projects.
Products
Innovative, high-performance products for new construction, repairs and restoration.
Applications
Proven product solutions and resources for projects of any size, in any market.
Resources & Support
Professional resources designed to enhance your expertise.
Find A Dealer
Where to purchase Rapid Set® and Komponent® products.
HOMEOWNERS
Homeowners
For homeowners and do-it-yourselfers who like to DIY.
Products
Professional-grade products for new construction, repairs and restoration.
How To's
Inspiration for your concrete projects — from repairs and restoration to decorative and fun.
Concrete Basics
Useful resources that help you become more knowledgeable about cement and concrete.
Find A Store
Where to purchase Rapid Set® products.
PRODUCTS
Products
Innovative, high-performance products for new construction, repairs and restoration.
From A to Z
Alphabetical listing of Rapid Set® and Komponent® products
By Category
Innovative, high-performance products for repairs and restoration, flooring, grouting, pavements and overlays, stucco, shotcrete and fill, shrinkage compensating cement, sealants and adhesives, and additives.
CSI MasterFormat Divisions
CTS products organized by CSI MasterFormat subgroups and divisions.
APPLICATIONS
Applications
Proven product solutions and resources for projects of any size, in any market.
Adhesives & Sealants
Architectural
Bridges
Containment
Decorative
Facades & Finishes
Grouting
Flooring
Pavements (DOT & Municipal)
Pavements (Airports)
Post-Tensioning
Polished Concrete
Repair & Restoration
Shotcrete
Slab-On-Grade
Tilt-Up & Precast
Waterproofing
ABOUT
About
We’re a close-knit group of employee-owners who are grateful for our customers, and the opportunity to provide the industry with innovative products and exceptional service.
Our Story
With hard work and loyal customers, one repair and restoration product has grown into well over 70 building material products.
Brands
Rapid Set® cement products, made with calcium sulfoaluminate (CSA) cement technology. Komponent® shrinkage-compensating concrete products, made with Type K cement technology.
Innovative Technologies
Learn about the speed, strength, and sustainability of Rapid Set cement products, and way to minimize cracking and reduce joints and curling with Komponent.
Leadership
We’re the leadership team who is inspired by the mindset, work ethic, and integrity of our employee-owners.
Careers
We’re looking for the right people to join us. Perhaps that’s you.
CONTACT
SEARCH
PROFESSIONALS
Products
Applications
Resources & Support
Find A Dealer
HOMEOWNERS
Flooring
Pavements (DOT & Municipal)
Pavements (Airports)
Post-Tensioning
Polished Concrete
Repair & Restoration
Shotcrete
Slab-On-Grade
Tilt-Up & Precast
Waterproofing
ABOUT
PRIVACY
Privacy Policy (last modified on April 07, 2014)
CTS Cement Manufacturing Corporation ("CTS Cement") operates CTScement.com (the "Site"). This page informs you of CTS Cement's policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information received from users of the Site. CTS Cement uses your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in CTS Cement's Terms and Conditions of Use.
Information Collection and Use
While using this Site, CTS Cement may ask you to provide certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your name, email address, postal address and phone number ("Personal Information").
Log Data
Like many site operators, CTS Cement collects information that your browser sends whenever you visit this Site ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, pages of the Site you visit, time and date of your visit, time spent on those pages and other statistics.
Cookies
Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive. Like many sites, this Site uses "cookies" to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of this Site.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to CTS Cement, but no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While CTS Cement strives to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, it cannot guarantee absolute security.
Links to Other Sites
This Site may contain links to third-party sites that are not owned or controlled by CTS Cement. Unless otherwise noted, the entities owning any such links are not under CTS Cement's control, are not endorsed or sanctioned by CTS Cement, directly or by implication, and any information or materials provided on such links is not the responsibility of CTS Cement. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site.
You assume all risks associated with visiting any linked website, and CTS Cement makes no warranty or representation regarding any linked website or the information contained thereon.CTS Cement assumes no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party sites or services and strongly advises you to read the terms and conditions and privacy policy of any third-party site you visit.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
CTS Cement may update this Privacy Policy at any time without notice to you. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy on each visit to this Site.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
